Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/phuong-nguyen-a4b2581b2 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Page Layout

C++

Adobe InDesign

Certifications

Webflow Layouts Level 1 Certification

Webflow Certification exam, CMS Level 1

Webflow 101 Certification

Phuong Nguyen

UX UI Designer | Webflow Designer

Hanoi Capital Region

Summary

Hello! I'm a UX/UI designer with a background in Information Technology and education. Currently based in Hanoi.

I'm a creative person who strongly believes in a human-centred design approach and passionate about creating user-friendly interfaces. I fundamentally believe that design can improve people's lives, transform companies and change culture.

So I chose Webflow as the tool to deliver a comprehensive design experience to users. Follow my updates to learn more about Figma and Webflow.

My values are empathy, respect, and open-mindedness.

I am always open to receive new knowledge about UX UI design and Web development. Would love to connect with you!

Feel free to connect me via:

- Email: phuong1505hn@gmail.com

Experience

neliSoftwares UX UI Designer | Webflow Designer June 2022 - Present (2 years 10 months) Vietnam

DaiNamUniversity
Practise Instructor of Information Technology
September 2021 - February 2022 (6 months)
Hanoi, Hanoi, Vietnam

- Prepare lectures before class
- Introduce students to the history of computers

Page 1 of 2

- Guide students to practice with ASP.NET, Java, C++
- Score and evaluate students' practical skills

Nam Viet Corp UX UI Designer January 2021 - September 2021 (9 months) Hanoi, Hanoi, Vietnam

WINDSoft UI Designer June 2019 - May 2021 (2 years)

Hanoi, Hanoi, Vietnam

Education

Dai Nam University
Bachelor's degree, Information Technology · (August 2017 - August 2021)

ITPlus Academy
Certificate, Graphic Design · (July 2017 - December 2019)